<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="configuration.xsl"?>

<!-- Put site-specific property overrides in this file. -->

<configuration>

<property>
<name>http.agent.name</name>
<value>PunkSCAN</value>
</property>

<property>
  <name>http.agent.name</name>
  <value>PunkSCAN</value>
  <description>HTTP 'User-Agent' request header. MUST NOT be empty -
  please set this to a single word uniquely related to your organization.

  NOTE: You should also check other related properties:

        http.robots.agents
        http.agent.description
        http.agent.url
        http.agent.email
        http.agent.version

  and set their values appropriately.

  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>http.agent.version</name>
  <value>PunkSCAN-v1.2.0</value>
  <description>A version string to advertise in the User-Agent
   header.</description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>fetcher.threads.fetch</name>
  <value>5</value>
  <description>The number of FetcherThreads the fetcher should use.
  This is also determines the maximum number of requests that are
  made at once (each FetcherThread handles one connection). The total
  number of threads running in distributed mode will be the number of
  fetcher threads * number of nodes as fetcher has one map task per node.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>http.content.limit</name>
  <value>-1</value>
  <description>The length limit for downloaded content using the http://
  protocol, in bytes. If this value is nonnegative (>=0), content longer
  than it will be truncated; otherwise, no truncation at all. Do not
  confuse this setting with the file.content.limit setting.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>db.max.outlinks.per.page</name>
  <value>1000</value>
  <description>The maximum number of outlinks that we'll process for a page.
  If this value is nonnegative (>=0), at most db.max.outlinks.per.page outlinks
  will be processed for a page; otherwise, all outlinks will be processed.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>db.max.anchor.length</name>
  <value>1000</value>
  <description>The maximum number of characters permitted in an anchor.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>generate.max.count</name>
  <value>-1</value>
  <description>The maximum number of urls in a single
  fetchlist.  -1 if unlimited. The urls are counted according
  to the value of the parameter generator.count.mode.
  </description>
</property>

<property>
  <name>fetcher.verbose</name>
  <value>true</value>
  <description>If true, fetcher will log more verbosely.</description>
</property>


<property>
  <name>indexer.max.content.length</name>
  <value>-1</value>
  <description>The maximum number of characters of a content that are indexed.
  Content beyond the limit is truncated. A value of -1 disables this check.
  </description>
</property>

</configuration>
